[Music]
Hello, my name is Mohammad Jaya and I am
excited to share that I have received an
offer from ICICI Lombard as a Unit Sales
Manager. So, during my MBA program
from Pune Institute of Business
Management, I have learned about pricing
management, such as how to set smart
prices, which help companies stay
competitive and in their growing stage. I have also learned about
sales and negotiation
skills, such as how to deal with clients, how to
maintain relationships with them, and many other things which will
help me enhance
my skills. So, with this, I am ready
to dive into this dynamic opportunity with
ICICI Lombard, which will enhance my
skills and help me as well as my career growth. Thank
you.
[Music]